Thanks for watching.
Good evening.
Here we go.
It's been a long time, ladies and gentlemen.
It's been a while.
It's raining.
Family Embry.
Is it sunny out there?
It's been a long time.
Hi, everyone.
How are you doing?
How are you feeling?
Are you all right?
Are you all right? How are you?
Elle.
I'm fine, Ayaka.
That's good. That's...
That's good.
You have a great suntan.
That's for sure.
I probably still am, kind of.
It's a bummer.
I lost.I lost.
I really want to talk about the Famien.
About the Famien, you mean?
It was my first Famien.
Well, less than 5 days.
Well, it was really fun.
It was so much fun, I don't know what to do.
I don't know... I don't have the vocabulary.
It's not that I don't have a vocabulary
It was so much fun that I lost it.
I could tell you were having a really good time, Ema.
Really? I wish I had.
Oh, wow.
I don't know... getting soaked in the water...
It was really fun to perform like that.
I want to go back.
I want to do it again
What was your most memorable moment? Familien.
What do you remember?
I don't know.
I have a lot of things right now.
What do you remember?
I don't know...
What is it?Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Did you go to Halloween?
I'm so glad.
You went to Halloween?
Japan!
I really understand.
Japan is Mitsu
Me too.
Japan
Japan and
NES and
I really enjoyed all of them, but
What is it?
I liked the deep fried fries. I don't know.
We also performed Samagretta for the first time. It was a lot of fun.
Hey...
Japyong was amazing.
We did that Japyong on both the first and second day...
The amount of water on the second day was amazing.
I was like, "What? I didn't know it was this much water.
I was so surprised!
It was soaking wet.
I was so surprised.You scared the shit out of me.
But the wieners were soaking wet, too.
But seriously, Japan was a blast!
It was so much fun.
My voice is usually so...
You have a low voice.
Me?
My voice is...
I have a low voice.
Yes, you do.
It's usually like this.
It's low.
Hey.
Day one, I almost drowned in 10 piers of water. Day one... well, they were both good.
You know what I mean? They were both good.
But the NES part was really loud.
NES, is that it? The name part?
The name part.
The name part was, you know, too high.
I wrote about it in my blog before, but I couldn't do it at the rehearsal. I wrote about it on my blog before.
I wrote about it in my previous blog. I thought, "What am I going to do?
I thought, "What should I do? What should I do?
It was very expensive.
I think it was the most expensive part I have ever received from Ebichu. The last part in Japan is also expensive, but I think the part with the name of NES is more expensive.
I think the part with the name of NES is more expensive.I think the NES name part is more expensive.
Hey, I've had enough of this.
But it's amazing. It's new, it's like...
I practiced that height a lot since I got this part, and I was happy.
I'm so happy, but I'm glad you guys said it was so good.
I'm so happy!
But it was really good. Thank you.
I'm so happy.
Did you have fun at the Yagura?
It was fun!
It was so much fun!
I mean, I climbed a Yagura in Japan.
It was a lot of fun!
I was able to meet people who were a little bit far away from the family on stage.
I got to meet some family members who were a little far away from me on stage.
It was so much fun!
It was so much fun.
Throwing those water balloons was a lot of fun.
That was a lot of fun.
But it was so much fun, I don't know what else to do.
Shooting star.
Thank you so much for your quick comments.
I've never seen Japan run that fast before.
That's right.
He ran like that!I ran like that.
It's too bad it was the other way around.
You're right. It's this one.
I think it's the hair one.
I only went to the hair part.
That's too bad.
Have some shaved ice from Emma's food truck! Oh, thank you!
Oh yeah! I requested cheese balls and pita bread.
I'm sure Emma's has shaved ice and other things too.
I'm so happy, I'm so happy!
Did you eat everything on the menu, Emma?
I'm so happy! Thank you!
I'm so happy.
Was the pita bread good?
I'm so happy! Emma had pita bread on the morning of the first day!
It was delicious.
Delicious!
I bought a honey orange uni!
Thank you!!! I'm so happy!
I've got my own goods for the first time in this show, so...
I was so happy when they waved to me when I came close to them or when I passed by them on the aisle.
I found them! So many!
Oh! You have Ewa's inner ring! I was so happy!
It's so cute, isn't it?
So cute!So cute!!!
You should wear the uni and cheer me on with your inner circle! Thank you!
It's so full-body gear.
I'm so happy.
The inner ring is so cute.
Because the pictures are cute, you know.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm so happy.
Thank you for watching!
Emma wanted me to say Nico too, but it was cute.
Thank you.
You know, on the first day...
I was wondering which one it was.
That's what Nooka said.
I asked Emma to tell me at that time, too.
I was a little reserved.
I'm glad you're going to tell us more from now on.
Two and two.
Please do a lot from now on.
I don't know... other Famie episodes.
I don't know, but...
It's really interesting.
Natarin's...
It's all so beautiful.It's all so beautiful.
I think it's really beautiful.
I think it's really beautiful, but there are a few places where it's a little bit...
I don't know...
There are a few things that make me giggle.
But it's good.
Did you have a favorite photo?
I don't know.
I just love it! This is so good! Very well taken! Thanks a lot! and "You're smiling so much!
And then there were the ones that said, "He's laughing so hard! I'm sure you can probably guess what I mean.
Cocomi-san staring at the shaved ice.
Wasn't that just awful?
I didn't know people could open their mouths that wide.
I didn't expect them to open their mouths that wide.
I was so surprised.
That was my favorite!
I love eating shaved ice with the members!
Seriously, the shaved ice was delicious!
I had lemon and blue Hawaii.
I think that's when Emma was washing up.
That picture was too good!
It really was a iawash!
Oh, and the part where she had mouth cancer...
That was definitely a good shot too.
Mayonnaise is holding her hand.Mayonnaise is holding hands.
That's it. That's the part where they're all gagging.
That one is good too, mayonnaise.
The part where she's grabbing Aya's arm on the NES.
Right there.
Thank you so much for the heart!
Netori's pictures are so good, I saved them all.
I know, I saved them.
I saved so many!
I had so much fun at home.
And I don't know, I have a lot of memories of FAMIA.
Good evening. I'm working part-time.
Thank you very much. It's delicious.
Thank you for watching.
I'm so happy to see you.
I'm so glad to see you.
Beautiful!
It's really beautiful!
I cracked up at Emachi's impersonation of Tamiko.
I've never been asleep.
Thank you for watching.
Did Emachi do the watermelon splitting too? Yes, we did!
I did it with Mirei.
Did it split? It broke just a little bit.
We split it with a big bang at the end.I cracked it open with all my might at the end.
It was delicious!
I couldn't see it from the front block.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Okay, let's take a picture.
Let's see how beautiful it was.
I wonder what's next?
It was really fun!
But I had my hair done a little cooler on the second day.
And I had them change the stickers on here from hearts to stars.
So I was able to take on the second day with a cool haircut!
But I felt a little safer on the second day than on the first day.
I felt a little more at ease on the second day than on the first day.
The costumes are cute, aren't they?
The school uniform style costume and the goldfish style costume.
Goldfish-like costume
They were so cute!
After the "Bubuhibuhi" (Cry me a river)
Emoji fusion after the song "Blah blah blah, cry me a river
Why was that part taken out?
I don't know.
I didn't even know she had that expression on her face.
Like that...
I thought I had a more proper expression.I thought you looked a little more put together.
I didn't think you looked that dumb.
I'm gonna have to calm down a little bit.
If I don't.
Or you'll end up with a half-hearted expression like that.
You're right about the goofy look.
I see. You're right.
Well, I mean...
It was cute that he was moving in the opposite direction of the youthful zombies.
It's not cute.
I don't know why they went the other way.
That was terrible!
What kind of mistake?
I don't know...
To the right!
I'm going to the right!
I'll be careful
Your hair looks good.
I'm glad you like it.
Thank you very much.
I can't believe it hasn't been a year since you joined, you were amazing.
I'm so happy
Thank you so muchThank you very much.
I'm glad you could make it.
Did you have a good time the next day?
Of course I did.
How late did you sleep?
I slept till about midnight, but...
No, I'm not going to pick you up, Bai.
I got it.
Bai chan.
What are you going to do?
Good luck with that.
Well, I'm just up there now and I like it because it's funny and fun and cute and all-around good praise.
Thank you very much.
Good evening good evening good evening Mr. Asahiko good evening
I'm also having the best summer ever with my family!
Yes, a touch.
I'm going to let my hair grow long.
It's already grown long enough... and my hair is a bit uncomfortable.
My partner has 16 strands of hair.
I'm quitting short... I mean, I'm quitting...
I'm going to grow it out.
You've got more expression than when you first joined us.
Thank you very much.
Yes, I was a little more like this when I first joined.
I was like this when I joined.It was like this.
Maybe things have changed a little bit.
stone
Aah!
It's like an idol's word, coming out unexpectedly.
Oh, you say "ah"?
No, don't say that!
I've been waiting for you for a while now.
Thank you.
Really? I had long eyebrows a few months ago.
But it's been a while. I've always had a bob.
I wonder how it will turn out.
Encore matsuri...
I guess it's now official to call them Emachi at the encore Matsuri and Matsuri Chua. I call them a lot.
Yes, indeed. Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well, number...number sixteen, Emachi, then it became Emachi.
I hope you will continue to call me "Emachi-". Thank you very much.
I'm glad you don't call me Mr. Sakurai.
As you can imagine, if someone called me Mr. Sakurai, I would say, "Oh, oh!
It's a little bit difficult to call me that.
Emachi-That's nice. Oh, I'm glad.
Were you thinking of getting swamped now? Even your face is swamped with Familen.
Hmm?
Were you thinking about getting swamped just now?I was thinking about getting into the swamp now?
I mean, I'm never going to get into it, am I?
But if you've used my face, I'm gonna be...
It's sticky.
No, it's dry, but don't let it slip out.
The cheese balls were sticky and ridiculously good.
Oh! I'm so happy! Thank you so much!
The cheese ball was delicious.
I'm so glad.
You got me hooked on Zubu Zubu. I'm glad. Thank you.
I'm glad. It's the same with the Famien, the tour, the Famien, and so on,
After this concert, I'm glad to hear you say you're hooked on Emma Emma, or that you're done with Emma-chan,
I'm so happy when people say, "I'm done with Emma Emma," or "I'm done with Emma-chan.
I'm so happy.
Oh, I'm fine, huh?
She said she's safe. I'm glad to hear that you're safe.
I'm also interested in Mr. Sakurayama.
If you are interested in her, please check her birthday first, and then find out what type she is.
Then I thought, "She's the same as me, so maybe she's a little too much into my personality. And then, I'll check out her Instagram!
Follow her! That was the goal.
From that point on, I just followed them on instagram and they appeared on their own. And then it's just like, "I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it!
It's great!
Let's all go to September 13! Thank you so much!
We're looking forward to seeing you! Sure, if you've been paying attention lately.
If you're interested in September 13, I hope you'll leave it open.September 13, I hope you keep it open.
I'd be happy to.
I'm a Gandhani fan, not an Emma fan. Oh.
That's the pattern, isn't it?
Is it usually the other way around? Usually...
She says she likes Emma.
Then she tells me she's in a show called Kanna-Unior.
I think it's normal for them to like both of them.
Well, even if you're a Gambandani fan, I'm happy.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy I'm getting through August looking forward to your birthday live!
Oh, well...
I'll get through it... but... there's a lot of shows coming up in August, too.
September 13th will be here soon.
Soon, I'm sure. Good evening.
It's been almost a year since I auditioned and fell in love with Manuma.
Wow! I'm so happy!
I'm glad to hear that you're hooked on Manuma since the audition.
But it's true, it's been almost a year since the audition.
That's fast!
It's early!
The afterglow is so strong that every time I see something orange, I think of Emma.
I'm so glad, but Emma's also been a bit of a loser lately.
But Emma has also been reacting really well lately.
I get so excited when I see that orange.I get so excited when I see that orange and stuff.
Good night.
Was it September 5 when you heard the acceptance announcement?
That's right.
So, on September 5th.
It's been just one year.
I guess.
But it's October 1st.
In case you're wondering, that's a tough one.
More orange stationery.
No kidding? I'm so happy. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
If you just like orange or something...
Sorry.
It's officially October 1st.
Yes! That's right.
I bought my first orange star.
An orange star?
What's so great?
I can't believe how fast the year has gone by.
Yeah, it's sure flown by.
You're right.
I'm preparing a cake for Eva's generation.
What's that?Huh?
Cake baking practice
Thank you, beautiful.
Eva, too.
She was into baking for a while.
She was into it.
She was baking for a while.
What should we do? We only have until 8:50 p.m.
I'd like to talk about her birthday, but there's not much to talk about, so all I can say is "Come!
I don't know if you're all going to come.
I wonder how many of you will come...
I wonder how many of you will come.
I was thinking...
Already...
I think it's almost decided.
Of course I'm going.
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I won't choose not to go.
I'm so happy.
Ematis Etang is my motivation.
I have to do my best
I'm gladI'm so happy!
Wait, wait, wait. Emachi says thank you for being born.
If you thank me so much...
I feel like, "Thank you for being born, Emachi
Thank you for being born
I don't get that many thank yous
I'm super happy
Say you're super happy.
It's just a normal thing to say.
I've never been thanked like that before.
That's nice of you.
That makes me happy.
I'm glad.
It's just...
Emma's, uh... fans'
frustration...
I don't know.
Last time I was in the showroom, you said the Honey Rangers were cool.
So...
You said you'd think of something before the birthday.
What?
A little...
You said you'd think about it.You said you were thinking about a little... a little.
I've been thinking about it all day.
I've been thinking about it a lot, and I've come up with a lot of ideas, but...
But I just don't have a clear idea.
But... my mom is with me.
My father is thinking about it with me, too.
I don't know...
I'm trying to get my mom to tell me that Emma's fans... what do you call them?
What kind of people are Emma's fans?
So I'm wondering if the people who are Emma's fans...
I'm like this, after all. I'm like, "Oh, my God, I'm such a fan!
I don't know...
Sometimes I wonder if I said something like "a few twists".
But they're the kind of people who say "good luck" to me, so maybe I'm a bit of a donan, but they're all really nice people.
I think they're all very kind people.
I'm really sorry about the way I feel about friends.
And there were a lot of people who told me that it was like talking to a friend at the scoring session.
So, you know, I've been thinking about all these things.
I'm trying to decide on a generic name, but it's difficult.
It's difficult, isn't it?
But you know what?
I've been saying this for a long time.
I don't know what it is that Emma thinks.
I want them to get along with each other.I really want you guys to be friends, don't you?
It makes me happy to be able to share fun things with you.
So if there's someone next to you wearing orange or something like that...
So if there's someone next to you who's wearing orange or something, you feel free to talk to them...
You talk about it. Oh, a rainbow!
It was like a catsuit. It was so cute.
I'm sure there are people who want to go to the show alone.
I'm sure there are people who want to go to shows alone, so I'd like them to enjoy it.
Even now, there are times when I want some alone time.
I don't know if it's like that for Type B, but...
I don't know if that's true of Type B people, but I definitely value my alone time a lot.
That's why.
Of course there are times when I want to talk to my mom or dad.
But she also wants some alone time.
I don't know why I did that.
That's why...
I want it.
What's this?
I don't know, it's just a way of looking at it.
A, you know what I mean? I think we all need some alone time, no matter what we've decided.
You know what I mean?
Alone time is important.
I'm a type B, so I get it.
No, but you're right... there are people who understand it even if they're large.
Alone time is really important.Seriously, people's time is important.
So the conclusion is that
I haven't decided on a general name yet.
I haven't decided on a generic name yet.
So today, I'd like to ask you
I'd like to hear what you think of it.
But I thought that Friends is really cute.
Like friends.
Like friends... who are kind and friendly... and cute.
Like Angoo.
Friends is so cute!
I don't know...
Like the Honey Rangers.
It was cute.
I thought it was really cute.
I thought Friends was more...
It's kind of unstable.
It's kind of horse-like.
My mom told me.
Friends Sakurai looks like a comedian.
That's true.
Sounds like someone I'd like to meet.
It's hard to tell.
You know, it's so fast.
I take it so seriously. I take it so seriously.I'm serious. I'm so serious.
Just the bangs, okay? Now.
Deliver bangs.
Smile Friends, Honey Friends.
Oh, I knew you'd have Honey Friends.
Emansion.
In Residents
Furefre Emmaolens
Ugh, Honey Friends looks good
Freh Freh Friends
Oh, thank you for 1,000 people!
I don't like this... Suddenly it's all gnarly...
Hmm...
Smiley, Emachi, Emmael Friends.
Emmael Friends. They're combining all kinds of things.
Souffle.
Emmael Friends. Fren Wangs.
Are your bangs okay today?
The bangs are... Well...
Sixty points.
Hanifure.
How about Emma Miles Friends?
It's so lush!
But you're right, the smiley face is cute too.
Emma FriendsEmmer Friends
emmer frens cute
Numanchu.
Oh, he's so cute! Numanchu!
I squished his bangs. You need to squash his face more.
Emma Chi, my friend, you're so cute.
You'll have to do it later. I'll do it. I love the Emma Emma Emma friends.
Emma Numah Friends. Oh, he's so cute.
Emma's manumatic friends.
I know, I know, I know, I know, I know.
Oh, my God, you guys are so funny.
Oh, my God. You know, the family's so funny.
They're all funny at all.
Emma numa Friends. I like it.
Emma.
Emonofriends Like the animal friends.
Emma's Children, Emma's PTA, Emma's Smile Protection Society, Emma's Swamp Group. Yeah.
Emma Swamp Group.
Emma Friends Emma Friends Simple, isn't it?
Emma's Smile Society, Honey Sunny Friends.
She said it's hard.
EGC Emma's no longer a part of it. That's funny.
Swamp Standing
hmmm
Waiting for picture FriendsFriends Waiting for Pictures
It's getting more and more like a big joke.
Oh, that's it.
It's turning into a comedy contest.
Friends swamp
Oh, is that it? It's like...
It says "people"...
It's like, "Emann-note"? This...
Frencu.
Heh...
Wow, it's so long!
Thousandony
Thousand
Oh my god, I can't, I can't, I can't, I don't know, I don't know
smiley face gummy
Emundo
Like Lemands
Nikonicoli
Friends Sapporo
Already
Oh, no!
Round pictures, round pictures... What's wrong with them?
It's cute, but...
But there were a few who answered well.Well, some of them... some of them... some of them were good answers.
Think about it. Well, everyone's thinking about it.
There were a lot of people who took the interesting route and gave it serious thought.
So, taking that into consideration...
I wish I could tell you before the birthday, but...
I'll do my best to come up with a good one.
I hope we can come up with a good name.
I'll try my best to come up with a good one.
Dru.
Good, good, good.
I wonder if everyone will wear orange for the birthday party.
I wonder if the venue will be honey orange. It'll be so beautiful!
Thank you for the psyllium.
Thank you for coming tonight.
I'm so excited!
I wonder...
Oh, my God.
Already.
We have a set list.
It's all set.
But most of it's already decided.
It's all set. So look forward to it.
Thank you for bringing the megaphone.
Can I decorate the megaphone? Can I decorate the megaphone? Decorate it.
I mean, we all have our favorite stickers and stuff, right?I was just wondering if you guys have any favorite stickers or...
I was wondering if there was anything you wanted to put on it.
I made it simple, so by all means.
You can add your own personal touch.
Please make them pretty.
Do you have stickers with pictures of Emachi? Thank you.
Are they raising the bar? No, no, no. If you want to make use of the material, leave it as it is.
It's fine.
That looks amazing, and I can't wait to see it.
I can't wait for September.
But there's a lot of love before that.
So, uh, we're up to 50 minutes.
Let's see...
Questions! I want you to ask me a question.
I don't want you to ask questions.
Questions.
I want to ask you this.
Please write it down.
Lemmons made a mistake.
I made a mistake.
Ask a question.
What's for breakfast today?
Today's breakfast is four sushi rice balls and a piece of chocolate.
Why bedrock valley?
I misspelled "iwaban-yoko" and read "iwaban-tani.I mistakenly read bedrock sideways as bedrock valley.
I like NES too much.
Thank you very much.
I'm so glad.
Do you play a lot of NES cover songs? Half and half.
Who is your favorite artist? I like Aimyon.
Did you eat ice cream today? I ate something today,
I had some kind of deep-sea jelly.
I had some kind of fruit on it.
What is your favorite food? Bread and ice cream.
Emachi, only your bangs are in the picture. I'm sorry.
I like Emachi too much.
Well, these questions are like that, please keep it that way.
I also listen to hip-hop. I listen when you dance.
Are you a dog person? Cat person? I am a dog person.
Are you good friends with Tamiko?
I am good friends with Ayaka Yasumoto, but I only met Tamiko for one day.
She is Emachi's type of guy.
I am glad to hear that. Thank you very much.
What is your favorite hiragana?
When it's screentime, do you have a screentime with bangs?
Yes! A scrunchy with bangs.
What was your favorite school lunch?
My college sister's fried bread.
Is there a hair color you would like to dye?Do you have a hair color you would like to dye?
Well, if I could do it for one day, I'd dye it gold.
I'm not good at ball games, how about you?
Well, I'm surprisingly good at ball games, I was 9 meters when I threw the softball.
Well, do you have any recent cosmetic recommendations?
What's your latest cosmetic recommendation?
Uh... well... Monjo Ion's glitter glitters!
The next new...
Oh, I said it!
Why?
Do you go to karaoke with your mom?
My mom doesn't tell me I'm too good at it.
Well...
Oh?
Hmm.
Did you get the report?
Uh...
No comment.
Mm-hmm.
Hmmm...
I'd like to live in Emma Chu's tear ducts.
Heh! I don't have tear ducts.
Actually, I don't have them.
Well...
Have you decided to finish high school?Are you ready to graduate from high school?
I've been trying to finish since the beginning.
Do your father and mother ever fight?
Your father and mother?
I don't see them.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best tomorrow.
Oh, no.
What prefecture would you like to visit?
I want to go to Australia!
I sent a picture of Emma to my friend and she said she was my type.
Thank you, friend.
Where does the name Emma come from?
It means "to be accepted overseas" in Japanese.
I just got it wrong.
I got the wrong prefecture.
If it was a prefecture...
Hokkaido.
I want to go there with my family.
You're good in space, Emma.
I wonder if I can talk to her.
With someone.
And then you can ask the others.And then I'll go ask the guys.
I'm gonna go ask them what they want to hear.
I think I'm gonna make friends with an alien.
I wonder what that would be like.
How tall are you now?
160, maybe.
Screws... hmm? Screws are flying.
I heard that if you give your head a tap...
I heard that when you get hit on the head, a few screws fly off.
Some of them are flying off because of the smack.
Do you want to be taller?
I was hoping for 163.
Is he still growing? No, I haven't.
I'm planning on getting a ponytail.
When my hair grows long enough, I will wear a ponytail.
What hairstyle do you want now?
When it grows a little longer.
I'd like to wear it here.
I'm still growing it out.
You're right, it's all about spirit.
Let's go for it!
Let's get mom and dad to pull us up and down.
Hmm...
Which do you like better, pictures or blood?
Blood.Mmmm... blood.
Hmmm...
Like a curly picture town.
Oh, I want to curl it when it grows so
I like Ema's eyebrows too much for Halloween.
Yeah.
They kind of turn into Halloween, don't they?
Like so and so
Halloween!
Have you decided on a birthday present? I haven't decided... I don't know what I'll do...
I want to go bouncing around town again. I want to do it.
How can I get better at making love? I don't know. I think I'll end up like Emma.
I don't know... how to make love hands work... it's difficult.
My lucky number is 16.
What did Yunami give you for your birthday?
Hair oil.
I also gave her candy that helps her save money.
Tell us about your recent episodes with YoonA.
We recently went to Kentucky together.
We decided to go there again.
We decided to go here later.
If you were a brother or sister, which would you want?
Big brother or big sister.
I want to know what ice cream you recommend right now.
Definitely Seven's ice chocolate ice cream is really good!Definitely Seven's ice chocolate ice cream is really good!
The member with the best Emaci moniker in Emaci's opinion.
You're that good.
I don't know, they all sound like Emma to me.
Yuno-chan?
Yuno-chan.
I like Emma.
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy all of a sudden.
Emaci, do you like Myss in the winter? Yes, I do.
You did a good job, Maya.
You're right. It's easy to see the characteristics.
I don't know.
But now... you know... in school...
I've never had friends imitate me before.
So I was surprised to see so many people copying me, but I'm really happy.
I'm a long hair person, so when I heard that you were planning to grow your hair long, it stopped my tears.
You and Yunopi seem to be getting along well lately, when did you think you were getting closer?
When was the last time you thought you and Yunopi were getting closer?
Musha Shugyo
I wondered if you and Yunopi got along during Musha Shugyo.
I thought so.
Are you a bob person? Bob?
I think I'm a bob person.I think he's a Bob fan.
Mr. Sakurai?
Yes! I'm Mr. Sakurai.
When you made the mistake of saying "How's Hartz today?", Junie definitely drooped around me.
Really?
I'm a fan of Yuno now.
I'm so happy! Thank you very much.
I took a picture of you and Yuno at the phone view. I hope I can give it to you someday.
Have you played with the Nerunerunerunerunerunerunerunerunerunerunerunerunerunerunerunerun? I haven't. I want to.
Do you take notes seriously in class? Do you doodle?
Notes? Oh, I do doodle.
I'm a fan of Emma Yunoyuna. Thank you very much.
I'm a fan of Emma Yunoyuna.
When I saw you at the show, your skin was so beautiful I fell down.
I'm so happy.
What is your favorite dish of your mother?
Curry.
Have you seen Beluga?
I've never actually met her in person,
I would like to meet him someday and say hello to him and tell him I've heard him call me Beluga.
Do you still like Snoopy? Yes, I do.
Love forever.
I like the middle 4 trio. I am so happy. Thank you very much.
Greetings are important. Yes, greetings are important.
Is Sakurai family's curry spicy?Is Sakurai family curry spicy?
I don't think so. It's about normal.
I answered in a very barbaric way.
If I write you a fan letter, will you read it? Of course! What would you like to talk about with Cocona?
We've been talking about going to Korea. I'd like to go there someday.
Oops, I got over the spicy food.
It's sharp and tasty.
I can now eat Tiger Tongue without any problems.
It's not good.
I don't know...
I don't know what it is, but...
I don't know why.
I can now eat Tiger Tangmen.
Then Yuna told me...
Emma.
I told her she's under a lot of stress.
I see...
I see.
Oh my god.
But now that I'm here...
Lately...
I've been saying I want to eat a frog.
Oh, let's do scooper time.
Wait a minute.Wait a minute.
I'll give you two minutes.
Here we go.
I'm sorry, that was sudden.
vellil
I'm in a convenience store these days.
I don't know what else to do.
When I'm doing squash time...
They get mad at me.
They ask me to stop a little longer.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I said, "Please cut me off.
Where are you going to use this picture?
Gal
Gals!
She's so cute!
I wanna play.
Hey.
The tension is really crazy.
That's right, next week's showroom.
Next week is mountain color, so please, please, please, please, please, please, please...
Please take a look.
Do your best coconut imitation.
Coconut!Coconut Girl
Imitate me, coconut.
It's hard.
Oh, and one more thing.
Thanks for watching.
It's growing.
I only have five minutes left.
I only have five minutes.
That's fast.
You're early, guys.
Let's see...
Tomorrow.
Uh...
I have a live concert
I have a live concert.
If you're going to be there tomorrow, let's meet up!
Let's meet up!
And then, in 15 minutes.
Berryz KOBO Soul Club starts at 9:00.
See you there!
Please be ready to listen.
Get ready to listen and wait!
And,
I...I...
Oh, thank you 1,300.
Thank you very much.
Also, I...
I'm going to work on TikTok a little bit more.
I'm going to work a little bit harder on TikTok.
I'm going to upload more things like Emma.
So please follow me on TikTok and wait for me!
Also, please follow me on TikTok.
Of course, there will be a birthday live on September 13th!
I'm going to have a live performance for my birthday.
It will be my first birthday live.
And I like to sing a lot
And I also like to dance.
I'm thinking a lot about how I want to express "Sakura heimai" (dance to the cherry blossoms) in my live performance.
If you're not sure about it, don't waste any more time to think about it!
Please get your tickets and wait until September 13th.
Please wait until September 13th!
Yes!
It's going to be great, it's going to be great!
I wonder if they will sing 40 songs.
Forty songs, indeed.
I'll probably be choked up at the end.
Will there be 20 songs for encores?
Yeah, maybe 20 encores.Yeah, and about 20 encores.
If we do about 20 encores, I think I'll be fine with just my raspy voice now.
So you have no choice but to go to the center live?
Yes, that's right.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Come on.
I'll do your voice.
I've already heard it all... on stage.
That's possible.
I'd sing for Emachi. Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to the day of your birthday, too.
The encore for the birthday encore will be Emachi.
You're right, it's "Emachi" now. Let's unite!
Please tell everyone who has to work tomorrow too!
Saito!
Good luck!
Don't cancel your work.
Even if you don't want to...
Let's go.
Let's go for it.
Eva's gonna do her best.
Don't worry. You'll be fine. Just hang in there at work.
I don't know. I'm supposed to go to the next show.
Good luck with that.
I'll do my best, Emma.Emma will do her best.
I want some cake.
Oh, let's up the rankings.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Hmm? I'm sorry, I'm so close.
Let's see...
First place goes to Mr. Bertie, thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Berg, for coming in second.
Thank you, Mr. Taremochi, for third and third place.
4th place goes to Kaven, thank you!
Thank you, Shunno-san for coming in fifth place!
I read from the top!
No.6 is Shigeru-san, thank you!
7th place goes to
I can't see 7th place!
Thank you, Tasusan!
No.8, thank you, Ore-san!
9th placeThank you, Runachi-san!
Thank you, Shimo-san (No.9) Thank you, Hoshina-san (No.11)
Thank you, Kunisan (No.12) Thank you, Hohowa (No.13)
I read from No.1 by mistake for the first time.
So, thank you very much everyone!
If you can see me at the show tomorrow, let's meet up again!
Bye-bye! Thank you!Bye-bye. Thank you.
Beautiful.